

## Contact

- Po Box 222 Uaq, Uae
- mohammedsaidali69@gmail.com
- https://dev-saeedali.netlify.app
- in www.linkedin.com/in/moham med-said-ali

# **Education**

# **Brillianz Group**

Certificate of Bachelor of commerce 2020- 2022

# The English School

Certificate of Class XII 2016 - 2018

2016 - 2018

### The New Indian School

Certificate of Class X March - 2016

# **Technical Skills**

HTML5

CSS

Javascript

\_ . . .

Bootstrap

Sass

React Js

# Mohammed Said Ali

# Front End Web Developer

# **Work Experience**

#### **Accounts Assistant**

#### Amrut Pure Drinking Water | Al Salamah Uaq

Sep 2021 - Nov 2021

- Received and verified employees' expense reports to cut expense reimbursements.
- Coded all transactions according to the internal company system to avoid errors.
- Prepared financial reports for senior managers to aid in the budget processes and support accurate decision making.
- Compiled data from cashiers, balanced drawers and prepared daily deposits.

#### **Cutomer Service**

## Feb 2020 - May 2021

# Cititrans Logistics L.L.C | Sharjah

- Placed outbound calls to existing members to provide additional consultation on products and services.
- Responded to customer questions and complaints and documented consumer communications.
- Researched assistance requested and offered accurate information to resolve issues and respond to inquiries.
- Communicated and followed up with prospective members via phone or email to process pending account applications.
- Addressed customer concerns and complaints and resolved issues promptly.

#### **Languages Known**

- > Malayalam
- > Hindi
- > English

#### Summary

Self-Taught Front end developer with more than 1 year experience working with Html, Css, Javascript, Bootstrap, Sass and React js. Highely adept in both independent and collaborative projects, with an emphasis on landing page and website development.

# Reference

#### Sameer

Hr Manager, Cititrans Logistics LLC

**Phone:** 971-56-547-1599

Email: Shameerkp613@gmail.com